# **JONATHON JACOBS**

(803) 240-0742



# **WEB DESIGN**

jrjacobs24@gmail.com

### SUMMARY

Consistently driven to learn and pursue new ventures and skills. People oriented with over three years in customer service. Strong and consistent performance in both team member and leadership roles. Have skill-sets in HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript, PHP, Photoshop, Dreamweaver, and Wordpress. Actively working as a freelance web-designer with professional clients to establish their web and social media presence.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **College of Charleston**

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Computing In the Arts 2010 – 2014

# **Charleston Southern University**

Secondary Education and Teaching 2008 – 2010

### **EXPERIENCE**

# WORK

#### **Staff Writer**

CultureMass, www.CultureMass.com March 2013 to Present

- Deliver well-written reviews and in-depth articles
- Meet deadlines assigned by editor
- Utilize Wordpress Dashboard and visual/text editor

#### Server

Longhorn Steakhouse, North Charleston, SC May 2011 to Present

- Provide guests with extensive knowledge and quality service to ensure guest satisfaction
- Cash handling and Sales
- Deliver high quality performance in a fast paced work environment
- Interact as a member of a cohesive team

#### Audio/Visual Deparment Aid

Charleston Southern University, North Charleston, SC August 2008 to May 2010

- Provide Audio/Visual assistance to CSU Staff
- Display extensive knowledge of audio and visual technologies

# INTERNSHIP

#### Social Media Marketing Intern

The Modern Connection, Charleston, SC September 2013 to December 2013

- Assist in all areas of online marketing and social media
- Content Creation, Facebook Applications, and Strategy Development
- Graphic and Web Design







/JONATHONJACOBS